sendscraps.com 2017-11-30

# Privacy Policy - SendScraps.com

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site www.sendscraps.com. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring pages, computer platform, date/time, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the userнs computer tied to information about the user. Our site does not use cookies. However, Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may use cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the following advertising companies: Google Adsense, CPX Interactive, Epic Direct, Glispa. Please check their websites for respective privacy policy documents.

DoubleClick DART cookies  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting London, you may see London hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about music). DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting: [www.google.com/privacy/ads/](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/)

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in your Internet Security software. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

External Links  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Contact  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us: [info@sendscraps.com](mailto:info@sendscraps.com).
